sharetribe.com 2016-01-25

# Privacy Policy - Create a marketplace with Sharetribe

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Sharetribe we have a few fundamental principles:

* **We don’t ask you for your personal data unless we truly need it.**
* **We don’t share your personal data with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.**
* **We don’t store personal data on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.**

Sharetribe Ltd (“Sharetribe”) operates website sharetribe.com. It is Sharetribe’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any personal data we may collect while operating our websites.

### Collection of Personal Data

Sharetribe may collect following personal data:

* Basic information such as name, age, postal address, email address and phone number
* Details about user’s employer (name, address, phone number, ID and VAT ID)
* Authentication information such as sharetribe.com username and password, and if any third party servive (e.g. Facebook) is used to sign in, the user ID of that service.
* IP address
* Information relating to the customer relationship such as bought services, their start and end times and information on their use
* Billing information

Customers of Sharetribe can operate their own marketplaces using the sharetribe.com service. Collection and processing of personal data on each such marketplace is subject to the Privacy Policies of the respective marketplace along with any applicable laws, rules and regulations. Sharetribe is not liable for the collection and processing of personal data on such marketplaces.

### Purposes for Which the Personal Data is Collected

The personal data is collected for the purposes of making available the sharetribe.com and related services and for managing and administering Sharetribe’s customer relationships. In addition, if you are a registered user of a Sharetribe marketplace and have supplied your email address, Sharetribe may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Sharetribe and our products, as well as the various marketplaces built using the sharetribe.com service. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

### Aggregated Statistics

Sharetribe may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Sharetribe may monitor the most popular marketplaces on the Sharetribe.com site or screen the marketplaces to help identify spam. Sharetribe may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Sharetribe does not disclose personal data other than as described below.

### Disclosures of Personally Data

Sharetribe discloses personal data only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need that data in order to process it on Sharetribe’s behalf or to provide services available at Sharetribe’s websites. Sharetribe may disclose your personal data to its subcontractors or other such parties outside the EEA who assist Sharetribe in providing the Sharetribe.com service. Such disclosure are made in accordance with the applicable Finnish and European laws, rules and regulations. Sharetribe will not rent or sell personal data to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Sharetribe discloses personal data only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Sharetribe believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sharetribe, third parties or the public at large. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Sharetribe uses cookies to help Sharetribe identify and track visitors, their usage of Sharetribe website, and their website access preferences. Sharetribe visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Sharetribe’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Sharetribe’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Sharetribe, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Sharetribe goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Sharetribe may continue to use your personal data as set forth in this policy.

### Protection of Personal Data

Sharetribe takes all technical and organisational measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personal data. Access to personal data is limited only to those employees of Sharetribe and its subcontractors who need to know the data in order to perform their work obligations. Each person who has access to the personal data has a personal username and password.

### Contact details

#### Name of the register holding personal data:

User register of the Sharetribe service

#### Responsible organization:

Sharetribe Ltd  
Business ID (Finland): 2432359-2  
Address: Bulevardi 14, 00120 Helsinki  
www.sharetribe.com  

#### Contact person:

Antti Virolainen  
Bulevardi 14, 00120 Helsinki  
Phone: +358 50 5311793  

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sharetribe may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Sharetribe’s sole discretion. Sharetribe encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
